<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EchoSafe</string>
    <string name="caller_key">Baba</string>
    <string name="lorem_ipsum">
    </string>
    <string name="self_defense_heading">7 Self-Defense Techniques for Women Recommended by a Professional</string>
    <string name="sub_heading">Victor Lyalko, the acclaimed martial arts master, wrote a book where he described the most effective methods of self-defense to help women if they are attacked.</string>

    <string name="tip1_title">1. For starters, memorize the vulnerable places.</string>
    <string name="tip1_content">It doesn’t matter how big or heavy your attacker is because you can beat anyone if you know where the most vulnerable spots are. The main ones are the eyes, nose, throat, chest, knees, and groin. You can attack in any way you want, but to be on the safe side, you need to remember that the most effective moves are aimed at these areas.</string>

    <string name="tip2_title">2. The simplest and most effective moves</string>
    <string name="tip2_content">One of the best moves that will make any giant whimper or drop to their knees is grabbing the wrist. Grab the little finger and ring finger with one hand and the middle and index fingers with the other, and bend the wrist forward. If you can’t grab your opponent’s hand, hit them with a fist or finger between the collarbones or into their Adam’s apple.</string>

    <string name="tip3_title">3. If you were grabbed from the front:</string>
    <string name="tip3_content">If you are grabbed from the front and you can’t lift your hands, move your hands forward and make a fist in front of your pelvis. Then, hit the attacker’s nose with your forehead and the groin with your knee.</string>

    <string name="tip4_title">4. How to free your hands:</string>
    <string name="tip4_content">You can easily escape a stronghold if you remember the “rule of thumb,” which is to rotate your arm to the side of the attacker’s thumb. When your arm is under the attacker’s, pull your arm as strongly as you can.</string>

    <string name="tip5_title">5. If you were grabbed from behind:</string>
    <string name="tip5_content">To set yourself free, quickly bend back and try to hit the attacker with the back of your head. If you can’t, grab their leg and pull to make them lose balance.</string>

    <string name="tip6_title">6. If you were approached and grabbed from the side:</string>
    <string name="tip6_content">Hit the attacker’s temple, jaw, or nose with an arched elbow strike. Then hit the belly or chest and run.</string>

    <string name="tip7_title">7. If you were pushed against the wall:</string>
    <string name="tip7_content">If cornered, hit vulnerable spots based on your position. Use your palm to strike the armpit, neck, or jaw. A headbutt can also disorient the attacker.</string>
</resources>